<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Torento Engineering (PVT) Ltd</title><link>https://www.torento.biz/about-us/</link><description>Recent content on Torento Engineering (PVT) Ltd</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© 2022 Torento Engineering (PVT) Ltd</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 11:22:16 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.torento.biz/about-us/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://www.torento.biz/about-us/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 11:22:16 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.torento.biz/about-us/about/</guid><description>Welcome to Torento Engineering Private Ltd, your trusted source for cutting-edge shoe manufacturing machinery, cutting dies, and accessories. With a legacy that dates back to 1986, we have been the pioneers in Sri Lanka, revolutionizing the industry and setting new standards of excellence.</description></item><item><title>Vision</title><link>https://www.torento.biz/about-us/vision/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 11:22:15 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.torento.biz/about-us/vision/</guid><description>Our vision is to lead the way in industrial machinery manufacturing on the island by continuously identifying and developing innovative products that cater to the evolving needs of the industrial sector in Sri Lanka.</description></item><item><title>Mission</title><link>https://www.torento.biz/about-us/mission/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 11:22:14 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.torento.biz/about-us/mission/</guid><description>At Torento Engineering Private Ltd, our mission is to provide comprehensive industrial machinery solutions to entrepreneurs across all scales in the industrial sector.</description></item><item><title>Quality Policy</title><link>https://www.torento.biz/about-us/quality-policy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 11:22:13 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.torento.biz/about-us/quality-policy/</guid><description>At Torento Engineering Private Ltd, we are unwavering in our commitment to manufacturing machinery and equipment of the highest quality. Our focus is on meeting and exceeding customer requirements, ensuring their utmost satisfaction.</description></item><item><title>Strengths</title><link>https://www.torento.biz/about-us/strengths/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 11:22:12 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.torento.biz/about-us/strengths/</guid><description>As the renowned brand &amp;ldquo;Torento,&amp;rdquo; we take pride in our diverse range of over 50 machinery types catering not only to the shoe-making industry but also to various other sectors, including headwear, apparels, packaging, and more.</description></item><item><title>Qualities</title><link>https://www.torento.biz/about-us/qualities/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 11:22:11 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.torento.biz/about-us/qualities/</guid><description>As a group of companies, Torento Engineering Private Ltd upholds the following qualities:
Customer First: We place the utmost importance on customer satisfaction, ensuring their needs and expectations are met and exceeded.</description></item><item><title>Uniqueness</title><link>https://www.torento.biz/about-us/uniqueness/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 11:22:10 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.torento.biz/about-us/uniqueness/</guid><description>Torento Engineering Private Ltd offers a unique service to the shoe-making industry in Sri Lanka by providing tailored products and services that meet local requirements.</description></item></channel></rss>